cabanova.com 2017-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Cabanova

This privacy policy sets out how Cabanova GmbH uses and protects any information that you give Cabanova GmbH when you use this website.

Cabanova GmbH is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Cabanova GmbH may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25.08.2009.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title

  * contact information including email address

  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@cabanova.com](mailto:info@cabanova.com?body=&subject=)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

Cabanova GmbH will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties, unless the member has not adhered to our terms and conditions (e.g. created a phishing site) or is required by law to do so. In such cases of abuse of the Cabanova services, each individual case will be reviewed and personal information may be passed on to the relevant company or person who is the victim of the abuse. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the address listed at the bottom of this page.

### Newsletters

Cabanova GmbH uses email as the method of contact with its customers. When signing up to become a member of Cabanova, the user must agree to accept and cannot unsubscribe from non-promotional emails (e.g. emails containing invoices, support correspondence and subscription information). In order to stop receiving non-promotional emails from Cabanova GmbH is by cancelling relevant subscription to our services. 

Cabanova GmbH also sends promotional emails (e.g. special offers) periodically. 

Additional information collected for each sent newsletter is:

\- number of newsletter opens

\- number of clicks on each link inside a newsletter

Subscribe / Unsubscribe methodology for Cabanova promotional newsletters

Each newsletter subscription needs to be confirmed. The confirmation (double opt in) is done by sending an initial greeting email, where a user action is needed to confirm the subscription, by clicking the unique personalized confirmation link. This way we ensure that the user agrees upon joining the newsletter list, and that the email addresses are real. 

Each newsletter received has clear information about the sender and unsubscribe methods. The unsubscribe is fulfilled within seconds after clicking the unsubscribe link and no further communication will be sent to the users who have stated that they do not wish to receive the specified information, unless they choose to register to the newsletter again.

### Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when Cabanova makes changes to this privacy statement, we will highlight the changes on our homepage and email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

### Contact Cabanova GmbH about Privacy

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the information we collect and use, please contact us at:

Postal Address

Cabanova GmbH

Fürstenwall 228

40215 Düsseldorf

Germany

Telephone

+49 (0)211.30 33 185

Fax

+49 (0)211.3033435

Email
